https://www.lasvegasgolfadventures.com/policies.html

Terms & Conditions / Policies
Golf Package Booking Terms & Policies
Las Vegas Golf Packages Prices are per person based on double occupancy.
Double Occupancy: 2 Golfers Sharing One Hotel Room
Single Occupancy: 1 Golfer Own Hotel Room or 1 Golfer + 1 Non-Golfer Sharing One Hotel Room
Resort Fees & Taxes
Las Vegas resort fees average at $25 per night plus 12% tax, these fees have already been included in all packages unless otherwise specified.
Blackout / High Demand Dates
Package prices reflected on our website are not valid during the following dates:
December202130, 31
Blackout / High Demand Dates are subject to change based on golf course and hotel occupancy. Any change will be noted directly in package details. Please call 1-800-841-6570 if you would like more information on Blackout Dates.
Weekday and Weekend Clarification
Weekday
Hotel Stay is Sunday-Thursday
Golf Rounds Monday-Thursday
Weekend
Hotel Stay that includes Friday and Saturday
Golf Rounds Friday-Sunday
Las Vegas Golf Only Packages include
Green Fees
Shared Cart Fees
Practice Balls
All Taxes
Las Vegas Golf Only rates on our website are per golfer.
Privacy Policy
SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?
When you submit a form our website, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.
When you browse our website, we also automatically receive your computer's internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.
Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.
SECTION 2 - CONSENT
How do you get my consent?
When you provide us with personal information to request a quote, get rates or contact us via our online form, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.
How do I withdraw my consent?
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at
or mailing us at: Golf Adventures Marketing, Inc. 6830 W Oquendo Road Suite 203 Las Vegas Nevada United States 89118
SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE
We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.
Payment:
We do not collect any credit card or other forms of payment on our website. For your complete protection, all payments are done through our off-line system
SECTION 4 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES
In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.
Links
When you click on links on our website, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.
SECTION 5 - SECURITY
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.
SECTION 6 - AGE OF CONSENT
By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.
SECTION 7 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.
QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION
If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at
or by mail at Golf Adventures Marketing, Inc. 6830 W Oquendo Road Suite 203 Las Vegas Nevada United States 89118
Cancellation Policy
Cancellation for golf only packages is 72 hours prior to the first tee time. Golf and hotel packages require a 7 day notice prior to arrival. Cancellation policies are subject to change based on package requirements, any changes will be noted on the package itself. If you are unsure of your package cancellation requirements please call
1-800-841-6570 for more information.
Guarantees
We provide guarantees on all golf packages on our website which feature our partner golf courses and preferred hotels. We will beat any similar golf package found online, to utilize the guarantee, you must provide the original copy of your current quote from another website and/or business.
Las Vegas Golf Adventures has provided Las Vegas golf packages for clients since 1996, and is currently the leading golf packager in Las Vegas. With knowledgable PGA Pro's on staff, clients are assured a successful golf trip.
Contact Us
Privacy Policy / Terms & Conditions
news letter
Stay informed with the latest golf packages available. Exclusive golf packages at special rates including huge savings on Las Vegas hotels and golf courses!
contact us
Las Vegas Golf Adventures - Copyright 2015
Email:
Address: 6830 West Oquendo Road Suite #203, Las Vegas, NV 89113
1-800-841-6570
